Allan M. Cormack Papers MS018
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Meetings, ceremonies, lectures, and professional travel, 1974 -- 1997; MS018.004; 2.4 Linear Feet
  - MGH Groundbreaking, 1995; MS018.004.010.00063 (Box 10)
  - Argonne 15-16 Oct, 1995; MS018.004.010.00064 (Box 10)
  - Wurzburg, 1995; MS018.004.010.00065 (Box 10)
  - Smithsonian, 1995; MS018.004.010.00066 (Box 10)
  - Korea Acd Sci Tech, 1996; MS018.004.010.00067 (Box 10)
  - U. Cambridge, U.S., 1996; MS018.004.010.00068 (Box 10)
  - Cavendish Lab, 1996; MS018.004.010.00069 (Box 10)
  - Korea, 1997; MS018.004.010.00070 (Box 10)
- Curricular material, 1963 -- 1994; MS018.005; 1.2 Linear Feet
  This series contains material from binders and files containing lecture notes, homework assignments, exams, and syllabi for undergraduate physics courses taught by Cormack.
  This series is arranged by course number.
  - Loose Course Notes, MS018.005.011.00001 (Box 11)
  - Notes on Mechanics, 1969; MS018.005.011.00002 (Box 11)
  - Physics 11, 13, MS018.005.011.00003 (Box 11)
  - Physics 11, 13 Fall, 1971; MS018.005.011.00004 (Box 11)
  - Physics 11, 13 Fall, 1978; MS018.005.011.00005 (Box 11)
  - Physics 11, 13 Exam and Final Fall, 1978; MS018.005.011.00006 (Box 11)
  - Physics 11, 13 Old Exams, MS018.005.011.00007 (Box 11)
  - Physics 12, 14 Summer, 1979; MS018.005.011.00008 (Box 11)
  - Physics 13 Final Exam, MS018.005.011.00009 (Box 11)
  - Physics 13 Homework Solutions, MS018.005.011.00010 (Box 11)
  - P13, 1989; MS018.005.011.00011 (Box 11)
  - P13, 1989; MS018.005.011.00012 (Box 11)
  - Phys 13 Fall, 1989; MS018.005.011.00013 (Box 11)
  - P18, 1980; MS018.005.011.00014 (Box 11)
  - P18, 1981; MS018.005.011.00015 (Box 11)
  - Phys 31 Exam Answers, MS018.005.011.00016 (Box 11)
  - Phys 31 Loose Material, MS018.005.011.00017 (Box 11)
  - Phys 31, 1989; MS018.005.011.00018 (Box 11)
  - Phys 31 Sept, 1991; MS018.005.011.00019 (Box 11)
  - Phys 31 SP, 1992; MS018.005.011.00020 (Box 11)
  - Phys 31 Spring, Fall, 1993; MS018.005.011.00021 (Box 11)
  - Phys 31 Spring, 1994; MS018.005.011.00022 (Box 11)
  - Physics 32, MS018.005.011.00023 (Box 11)
  - Physics 32 - Loose Material, MS018.005.011.00024 (Box 11)
  - Physics 32, 1963; MS018.005.011.00025 (Box 11)
  - Physics 32, 1979; MS018.005.011.00026 (Box 11)
  - P 32, 1986; MS018.005.011.00027 (Box 11)
  - Miscell Phy 32 Stuff, MS018.005.011.00028 (Box 11)
  - MathCad and Excell Phy 32, MS018.005.011.00029 (Box 11)
  - Physics 32 Fall, 1993; MS018.005.011.00030 (Box 11)
  - P42, 1969 -- 1970; MS018.005.011.00031 (Box 11)
  - P42, 1982; MS018.005.011.00032 (Box 11)
  - Physics 42 Spring, 1983; MS018.005.011.00033 (Box 11)
  - Physics 42 Fall, 1991; MS018.005.011.00034 (Box 11)
  - Physics 42 Homework Fall, 1991; MS018.005.011.00035 (Box 11)
  - P43, 1973; MS018.005.011.00036 (Box 11)
  - P43, 1973; MS018.005.011.00037 (Box 11)
  - Physics 43 Polarization Normalization P-C, 1973; MS018.005.011.00038 (Box 11)
  - P61, 1965; MS018.005.011.00039 (Box 11)
  - Physics 131 Homework Solutions, MS018.005.011.00040 (Box 11)
  - P131 Solns, 1985; MS018.005.011.00041 (Box 11)
- Publications and presentations, 1945 -- 1997; MS018.006; 1.0 Linear Feet
  This series contains reprints of Cormack's publications; notes and overhead transparencies for scientific presentations; and video tapes of a 1997 interview of Cormack for Naked to the Bone, a television documentary about the history of medical imaging technology.
  - AMC rotation therapy, MS018.006.012.00001 (Box 12)
  - Lindau 87, MS018.006.012.00002 (Box 12)
  - Elastic and scattering, MS018.006.012.00003 (Box 12)
  - Scanning in medicine, MS018.006.012.00004 (Box 12)
  - Photometric use of plates, 1945; MS018.006.012.00005 (Box 12)
  - Momentum determination from cloud chamber, 1953; MS018.006.012.00006 (Box 12)
  - Interference of Rayleigh and nuclear Thomson scattering, 1954; MS018.006.012.00007 (Box 12)
  - Heat generation in the earth by solar neutrinoes, 1954; MS018.006.012.00008 (Box 12)
  - Resonance scattering of gamma rays by nuclei, 1954; MS018.006.012.00009 (Box 12)
  - Neutrinos from the sun, 1955; MS018.006.012.00010 (Box 12)
  - Internal Rayleigh scattering, 1955; MS018.006.012.00011 (Box 12)
  - Fourier transforms in cylindrical co-ordinates, 1957; MS018.006.012.00012 (Box 12)
  - Proton-proton scattering, 1958; MS018.006.012.00013 (Box 12)
  - Elastic scattering and polarization of protons, 1959; MS018.006.012.00014 (Box 12)
  - Semiclassical theory of internal Rayleigh scattering, 1959; MS018.006.012.00015 (Box 12)
  - Cormack computed tomography: history and some recent developments, 1960; MS018.006.012.00016 (Box 12)
  - Dead time losses, 1961; MS018.006.012.00017 (Box 12)
  - Diffraction by atoms, 1962; MS018.006.012.00018 (Box 12)
  - Normalization of p-p, p-d, and p-He, 1963; MS018.006.012.00019 (Box 12)
  - Representation of a function, 1963; MS018.006.012.00020 (Box 12)
  - Representation of a function II, 1964; MS018.006.012.00021 (Box 12)
  - Small-angle scattering, 1964; MS018.006.012.00022 (Box 12)
  - Effects of multiple scattering, 1964; MS018.006.012.00023 (Box 12)
  - Measurement of cross sections, 1965; MS018.006.012.00024 (Box 12)
  - Neutron total cross sections, 1968; MS018.006.012.00025 (Box 12)
  - Precise comparison of pi + and pi - lifetimes, 1968; MS018.006.012.00026 (Box 12)
  - University of CA, Ernest O. Lawrence Radiation Laboratory, 1968; MS018.006.012.00027 (Box 12)
  - Determination of the refractive index, 1969; MS018.006.012.00028 (Box 12)
  - An improved liquid hydrogen differential, 1969; MS018.006.012.00029 (Box 12)
  - Measurement of cross sections with neutrons as targets II, 1969; MS018.006.012.00030 (Box 12)
  - Charged-pion lifetime and a limit on a fundamental length, 1969; MS018.006.012.00031 (Box 12)
  - Videotapes, 1997; MS018.006.013.001 (Box 13)
  - Measurements of the lifetimes of positive and negative pions, 1971; MS018.006.015.00001 (Box 15)
  - In vivo determination of attenuation coefficients, 1974; MS018.006.015.00002 (Box 15)
  - Quantitative proton tomography: preliminary experiments, 1976; MS018.006.015.00003 (Box 15)
  - Algorithms for two-dimensional reconstruction, 1977; MS018.006.015.00004 (Box 15)
  - Sampling the radon transform with beams of finite width, 1978; MS018.006.015.00005 (Box 15)
  - Early two-dimensional reconstruction (CT scanning), 1979; MS018.006.015.00006 (Box 15)
  - Early Two-dimensional Reconstruction and Recent Topics Stemming From it, 1979; MS018.006.015.00007 (Box 15)
  - An exact subdivision of the radon transform, 1980; MS018.006.015.00008 (Box 15)
  - A radon transform on spheres, 1980; MS018.006.015.00009 (Box 15)
  - The future of the principles of computed tomography, 1981; MS018.006.015.00010 (Box 15)
  - The radon transform on a family of curves in the plane, 1981; MS018.006.015.00011 (Box 15)
  - Computed tomography: history and some recent developments, MS018.006.015.00012 (Box 15)
  - Computed tomography: some history and recent developments, 1982; MS018.006.015.00013 (Box 15)
  - The radon transform on a family of curves in the plane II, 1982; MS018.006.015.00014 (Box 15)
  - Radon's Problem - Old and New, 1984; MS018.006.015.00015 (Box 15)
  - Radon, 1985; MS018.006.015.00016 (Box 15)
  - The problem in rotation therapy with x-rays, 1987; MS018.006.015.00017 (Box 15)
  - A problem in rotation therapy with x-rays: dose distributions, 1987; MS018.006.015.00018 (Box 15)
  - Radon's problem for some surfaces, 1987; MS018.006.015.00019 (Box 15)
  - On a problem in radiotherapy: questions of non-negativity, 1989; MS018.006.015.00020 (Box 15)
  - The mathematics and physics of radiation dose planning using x-rays, 1990; MS018.006.015.00021 (Box 15)
  - Response to Goitein, 1990; MS018.006.015.00022 (Box 15)
  - 75 years of radon transform, 1992; MS018.006.015.00023 (Box 15)
  - My connection with the radon transform, 1994; MS018.006.015.00024 (Box 15)
  - A paraboloidal radon transform, 1994; MS018.006.015.00025 (Box 15)
  - Some early radiotherapy optimization work, 1995; MS018.006.015.00026 (Box 15)
- Papers by other scientists, 1931 -- 1990; MS018.007; 1.2 Linear Feet
  Physics and mathematics manuscripts, reprints, reports, and book chapters. Includes some patents by Godfrey Hounsfield, Cormack's fellow Nobelist for Physiology or Medicine in 1979. Papers published in journals readily available elsewhere that were not annotated by Cormack or the author have been discarded, but are listed by author:
  Entire Issues:
  The Journal of General Microbiology 4/1 (January 1950).
  Occasional Notes of the Royal Astronomical Society, Number 9 (June 1941).
  Proceedings of the Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers 66/5 (May 1978). [Cover labeled "Horn," probably referring to article in this issue by B. K. P. Horn, "Density Reconstruction Using Arbitrary Ray-Sampling Schemes."]
  Articles and Excerpts:
  Aaboe, A. "Scientific Astronomy in Antiquity." Philosophical Transactions of the Royal Society of London, A 276 (1974): 21-42.
  Aaboe, Asger. "On Babylonian Planetary Theories." Centaurus 5/3-4 (1958): 209-77.
  Aaboe, Asger. "The Insignificance of Fourier Expansions for the Understanding of Ptolemy's Models." Isis 51/4 (December 1960): 565.
  Allen, K. W., W. E. Burcham, and D. H. Wilkinson. "Interaction of Fast Neutrons with Beryllium and Aluminum." Nature 159 (April 5, 1947): 473-75.
  Alphonce, A. Johansson, and G. Tibell. "The Asymmetry of 155 MeV Protons Elastically and Inelastically Scattered from Carbon, Oxygen and Calcium." Nuclear Physics 4/5 (1957): 672-76.
  Archer, E. M. "The Crystal Structure of meta-dinitrobenzene." Proceedings of the Royal Society, A, vol. 188 (1946): 51-62.
  Askey, Richard. "Lecture 3: Fractional Integrals and Hypergeometric Functions." In Orthogonal Polynomials and Special Functions, Regional Conference Series in Applied Mathematics, No. 21 (Philadelphia: Society for Industrial and Applied Mathematics, 1975): 19-25.
  Atzmony, U., S. J. Norton, L. J. Swartzendruber, and L. H. Bennett. "Mossbauer Imaging: Experimental Result." Nature 330 (November 12, 1987): 153-54.
  Backlund, E.-O. "Stereostatic Radiosurgery in Intracrancial Tumours and Vascular Malformations." Advances and Technical Standards in Neurosurgery, vol. 6 (1979): 1-37.
  Barakat, Richard. "Solution of an Abel Integral Equation for Band-Limited Functions by Means of Sampling Theorems." Journal of Mathematics and Physics 43/4 (December1964): 325-31.
  Barnes, C. A. and A. P. French. "Angular Correlation Between alpha-Particles and gamma-Rays in the Reaction F19 (p,?alpha,gamma)O16." Nature 166 (July 22, 1950): 145-147.
  Barnes, C. A., G. H. Stafford, and D. H. Wilkinson. "Photo-electric Disintegration of the Deuteron at 6[dot]13 and 17[dot]6 MeV." Nature 165 (January 14, 1950): 69-70.
  Basson, J. K. and J. Steyn. "Absolute Alpha Standardization with Liquid Scintillators." Proceedings of the Physical Society, A, vol. LXVII (1954): 297-298.
  Bates, R. H. T., R. M. Lewitt, M. J. McDonnell, M. O. Milner, and T. M. Peters. "Practical Image Processing." Phys. Technol. 9 (1978): 101-07.
  Bates, R. H. T. and T. M. Peters. "Towards Improvements in Tomography." New Zealand Journal of Science 14: 883-96.
  Baumgart, H., W. Arnold, J. Gunzel, E. Huttel, A. Hofmann, N. Kniest, E. Pfaff, G. Reiter, S. Tharraketta, and G. Clausnitzer. "Proton and Helium Stopping Cross Sections in Gaseous Hydrocarbon Compounds." Nuclear Instruments and Methods in Physics Research B5 (1984): 1-9.
  Bellini, Sandro, Maurizio Piacentini, and Ciro Cafforio. "Compensation of Tissue Absorption in Emission Tomography." IEEE Transactions on Acoustics, Speech, and Signal Processing ASSP-27/2 (June 1979): 213-218.
  Benfield, A. E. "Thermal Consequences of the Capture of Neturinos by the Earth." The Physical Review 74/5 (September 1, 1948): 621.
  Berezin, A. A. "Can Life Be Based on a Single Chemical Substance?" Naturwissenschaften 71 (1984): 45.
  Berezin, A. A. "Fivefold Symmetry in Boron and Borides." Nature 314 (April 11, 1985): 500.
  Berezin, A. A. "Inherent Genetic Instability Due to the Presence of 14C-Atoms in Information Bearing Structures." Bulletin of the American Physical Society 29/635 (1984).
  Berezin, A. A. "Isotropic Biology." Il Nuovo Cimento 1/3D: 914-16.
  Berezin, A. A. "Simulation of a Structural Phase Transition on a Simple Electrostatic System." Physics in Canada 41/3 (1985): 30.
  Berezin, A. A. "Some Exact Results for 2D and 3D Kronig-Penney Model for Zero Binding Energy Delta Wells." Bulletin of the American Physical Society 30/524 (1985).
  Berezin, A. A. "Two Exactly Solvable Models for the Collapse o the Particle to the Center in a Nonrelativistic Quantum Mechanics." Lettere al Nuovo Cimento 2/40: 145-46.
  Berezin, Alexander A. "Bound States in the Field of Several Noncollapsing Inverse Square Potentials." American Journal of Physics 53/1 (January 1985): 69-71.
  Berezin, Alexander A. "Collectively Deactivating Excited Configurations of Impurity Systems in Electric Field--Electroluminescence and Switching." Journal of Luminescence 31 and 32 (1984): 188-90. Berezin, Alexander A. "Double Tunnel Jumps in Activationless Hopping Conductivity." Journal of Physics C: Solid State Physics 17 (1984): L393-97.
  Berezin, Alexander A. "Information Storage Based on Isotropic Combinations." Speculations in Science and Technology 7/5 (April 1984): 317-19.
  Berezin, Alexander A. "Isotopic Disorder as a Limiting Factor for the Mobility of Charge Carriers." Chemical Physics Letters 110/4 (October 5, 1984): 385-87.
  Berko, Stephan and Frank L. Hereford. "Experimental Studies of Positrono Interactions in Solids and Liquids." Reviews of Modern Physics 28/3 (July 1956): 299-307.
  Berko, Stephan and John S. Plaskett. "Correlation of Annihilation Radiation in Oriented Single Metal Crystals." Physical Review 112/6 (December 15, 1958): 1877-87.
  Berry, M. V. and D. F. Gibbs. "The Interpretation of Optical Projections." Proceedings of the Royal Society of London, A 314 (1970): 143-52.
  Besicovitch, A. S. "A Uniqueness Theorem and a Problem on Integration." Journal of the London Mathematical Society 33 (1958): 82-84.
  Bethe, H. A. "Scattering and Polarization of Protons by Nuclei." Annals of Physics 3/2 (February 1958): 190-240.
  Beylkin, G. "Distorted-Wave Born and Distorted-Wave Rytov Approximations." Optics Communications 53/4 (March 15, 1985): 213-16.
  Beylkin, G. "The Fundamental Identity for Iterated Spherical Means and the Inversion Formula for Diffration Tomography and Inverse Scattering." Journal of Mathematical Physics 24/6 (June 1983): 1399-1400.
  Beylkin, G. "Imagine of Discontinuities in the Inverse Scattering Problem by Inversion of a Causal Generalized Radon Transform." Journal of Mathematical Physics 26/1 (January 1985): 99-108.
  Beylkin, Gregory. "The Inversion Problem and Applications of the Generalized Radon Transform." Communications on Pure and Applied Mathematics 37 (1984): 579-99.
  Bjorck, A. and T. Elfving. "Accelerated Projection Methods for Computing Pseudoinverse Solutions of Linear Equations." BIT 19 (1979): 145-63.
  Bogdanov, I. V. and Yu N. Demkov. "Inverse Problems in Classical Scattering Theory for Centrosymmetric Electric and Magnetic Fields." Journal of Physics A: Mathematical and General 17 (1984): L155-57.
  Bracewell, R. N. and A. C. Riddle. "Inversion of Fan-Beam Scan in Radio Astronomy." The Astrophysical Journal 150 (November 1967): 427-34.
  Bracewell, R. N. and S. J. Wernecke. "Image Reconstruction Over a Finite Field of View." Journal of the Optical Society of America 65/11 (November 1975): 1342-46.
  Breit, G. and P. B. Daitch. "Correspondence between Semiclassical and Quantum Treatments of Coulomb Excitation." The Physical Review 96/5 (December 1, 1954): 1447-48.
  Brooks, Rodney A. and Giovanni Di Chiro. "Slice Geometry in Computer Assisted Tomography." Journal of Computer Assisted Tomography 1/2 (1977): 191-99.
  Brooks, Rodney A., Lloyd G. Mitchell, Christopher M. O'Connor, and Giovanni Di Chiro. "On the Relationship Between Computed Tomography Numbers and Specific Gravity." Physics in Medicine and Biology 26/1 (1981): 141-47.
  Brooks, Rodney A., Victor J. Sank, Walter S. Friauf, Stephen B. Leighton, Horace E. Cascio, and Giovanni Di Chiro. "Design Considerations for Positron Emission Tomography." IEEE Transactions on Biomedical Engineering BME, 28/2 (February 1981): 158-77.
  Calame, G., P. F. Cooper, Jr., S. Engelsberg, G. L. Gerstein, A. M. Koehler, A. Kuckes, J. W. Meadows, K. Strauch, and R. Wilson. Nuclear Instruments 1 (1957): 169-82.
  Cassels, J. M., G. H. Stafford, and T. G. Pickavance. "Proton-Proton Scattering at 146 MeV." Nature 168 (September 15, 1951): 468-70.
  Cassels, J. M., G. H. Stafford, and T. G. Pickavance. "Scattering of 146 MeV. Protons by Deuterons." Nature 168 (September 29, 1951): 168-69.
  Cha, S. and C. M. Vest. "Interferometry and Reconstruction of Strongly Refracting Asymmetric-Refractive-Index Fields." Optics Letters 4/10 (October 1979): 311-13.
  Chamberlain, Owen, Emilio Segre, Robert D. Tripp, Clyde Wiegand, and Thomas Ypsilantis. "Experiments with 315-MeV Polarized Protons: I. Elastic Scattering by Complex Nuclei." The Physical Review 102/6 (June 15, 1956): 1659-75.
  Chamberlain, O., E. Segre, R. D. Tripp, C. Wiegand, and T. Ypsilantis. "Experiments with 315-MeV Polarized Protons: Proton-Proton and Proton-Neutron Scattering." The Physical Review 105/1 (January 1, 1957): 288-301.
  Chapman, C. H. and P. W. Cary. "The Circular Harmonic Radon Transform." Inverse Problems 2 (1986): 23-49.
  Chen, Y. W. "On the Solutions of the Wave Equation in a Quadrant of R^4." Bulletin of the American Mathematical Society 70 (1964): 172-77.
  Chen, Y. W. "Solutions of the n-Dimensional Wave Equation in the Exterior of the Characteristic Cones (I)*." Indiana University Mathematics Journal 20/1 (1979): 33-55.
  Chen, Y. W. "Solutions of the Wave Equation in R^n+1 with Data on a Characteristic Cone." Bulletin of the Institute of Mathematics Academica Sinia 4/2 (December 1976): 205-08.
  Cherry, R. D., S. W. Fowler, T. M. Beasley, and M. Heyraud. "Polonium-210: Its Vertical Oceanic Transport by Zooplankton Metabolic Activity." Marine Chemistry 3 (1975): 105-10.
  Cherry, R. D. and L. V. Shannon. "The Alpha Radioactivity of Marine Organisms." Atomic Energy Review 12/1 (1974): 3-45.
  Chiu, M. Y., H. H. Barrett, R. G. Simpson, C. Chou, J. W. Arendt, and G. R. Gindi. "Three-Dimensional Radiographic Imaging with a Restricted View Angle." Journal of the Optical Society of America 69/10 (October 1979): 1323-33.
  Conroy, Glenn C. and Michael W. Vannier. "Endocranial Volume Determination of Matrix-Filled Fossil Skulls Using High-Resolution Computed Tomography." Hominid Evolution: Past, Present, and Future: Proceedings of the Taung Diamond Jubilee International Symposium, Johannesburg and Mmabatho, Southern Africa (1985): 419-26.
  Cousins, A. W. J. and R. Guelke. "Photoelectric Observations of Occulations at the Cape Observatory." Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society 113/6 (1953): 776-79.
  Craig, D. R. and M. P. Sirkis. "Simplified Apparatus for Producing Transaxial Tomograms." Materials Evaluation (October 1978): 20-23.
  Crowther, R. A., L. A. Amos, and A. Klug. "Three Dimensional Image Reconstruction Using Functional Expansions." Proceedings of the Fifth European Congress on Electron Microscopy (1972): 593-97.
  Crowther, R. A., D. J. DeRosiers, and A. Klug. "The Reconstruction of a Three-Dimensional Structure from Projections and Its Application to Electron Microscopy." Proceedings of the Royal Society of London, A, 317 (1970): 319-40.
  Crowther, R. A. and A. Klug. "Three Dimensional Image Reconstruction on an Extended Field-A Fast, Stable Algorithm." Nature 251/5475 (October 11, 1974): 490-92.
  Curling, C. D. and J. O. Newton. "Coincidences between Proton and Gamma-Rays in (d,p) Reactions." Nature 166 (August 26, 1950): 339-342.
  Daitch, P. B., J. P. Lazarus, M. H. Hull, Jr., F. D. Benedict, and G. Breit. "Validity of Semiclassical Treatment of Coulomb Excitation." The Physical Review 96/5 (December 1, 1954): 1449-50.
  Daniuk, S., G. Kontrym-Sznajd, A. Rubaszek, H. Stachowiak, J. Mayers, P. A. Walters, and R. N. West. "Selective Enhancement of Different Electron Populations by Electron-Positron Attraction: Application to Zinc." Journal of Physics, F, Metal Physics 17 (1987): 1365-78.
  Davis, Raymond, Jr. "Attempt to Detect the Antineutrinos from a Nuclear Reactor by the Cl37 (v,e-)A37 Reaction." The Physical Review 97/3 (February 1, 1955): 766-69.
  Davison, M. E. and F. A. Grunbaum. "Tomographic Reconstruction with Arbitrary Directions." Communications on Pure and Applied Mathematics 34 (1981): 77-120.
  Deans, Stanley R. "A Unified Radon Inversion Formula." Journal of Mathematical Physics 19 (1978): 2346-49.
  De Rosier, D. J. and A. Klug. "Reconstruction of Three-Dimensional Structures from Electron Micrographs." Nature 217 (January 13, 1968): 130-34.
  Devaney, A. J. "Inverse-Scattering Theory Within the Rytov Approximation." Optics Letters 6/8 (August 1981): 374-76.
  Devaney, A. J. "Inversion Formula for Inverse Scattering within the Born Approximation." Optics Letter 7/3 (March 1982): 111-12.
  Devaney, A. J. and G. Beylkin. "Diffraction Tomography Using Arbitrary Transmitter and Receiver Surfaces." Ultrasonic Imaging 6 (1984): 181-93.
  Dubal, L. "Proton Radiology with a 600-MeV Accelerator." Atomikornenergie (1976): 189-92.
  Durrani, T. S. and C. E. Goutis. "Optimisation Techniques for Digital Image Reconstruction from Their Projections." IEEE Proceedings 127 (September 1980): 161-69.
  Eggermont, P. P. B. "Tomographic Reconstruction on a Logarithmic Polar Grid." IEEE Transactions on Medical Imaging MI-2/1 (March 1983): 40-48.
  Evans, David S., J. C. R. Heydenrych, and J. D. N. van Wyk. "Observations of Occulations of Antares with the Radcliffe Reflector." Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society 113/6 (1953): 781-85.
  Falconer, K. J. "The Determination of a Function from Its Projections." Monthly Proceedings of the Cambridge Philosophical Society 85 (1979): 351-55.
  Ferrell, Richard A. "Theory of Positron Annihilation in Solids." Reviews of Modern Physics 28/3 (July 1956): 308-22.
  Frahn, W. E. "On the Nucleon-Nucleus Interaction." Il Nuovo Cimento 10/4 (1956): 313-22.
  Freeman, Joan M. and A. S. Baxter. "Short-Range Gamma-Particles from the Disintegration of Sodium, Aluminum, and Fluorine by Protons." Nature 162 (October 30, 1948): 696-99.
  French, A. P. "Matrix Elements for Octupole Radiative Transitions." Philosophical Magazine, Ser. 7, vol. xlii (March 1951): 263-66.
  Friedman, Marvin I., John W. Beattie, and John S. Laughlin. "Cross-sectional Absorption Density Reconstruction for Treatment Planning." Physics in Medicine and Biology 19/6 (1974): 819-30.
  Fuller, E. G. and Evans Hayward. "Nuclear Elastic Scattering of Photons." The Physical Review 101/2 (January 15, 1956): 692-700.
  Fulton, Thomas and Fritz Rohrlich. "Classical Radiation from a Uniformly Accelerated Charge." Annals of Physics 9/4 (April 1960): 499-517.
  Gilbert, Peter. "Iterative Methods for the Three-Dimensional Reconstruction of an Object from Projections." Journal of Theoretical Biology 36 (1972): 105-17.
  Goiten, M. "Three-Dimensional Density Reconstruction from a Series of Two-Dimensional Projections." Nuclear Instruments and Methods 101 (1972): 509-18.
  Goldhaber, M. and E. Teller. "On Nuclear Dipole Vibrations." Physical Review 74/9 (November 1, 1948): 1046-49.
  Gordon, Richard, Robert Bender, and Gabor T. Herman. "Algebraic Reconstruction Techniques (ART) for Three-Dimensional Electron Microscopy and X-Ray Photography." Journal of Theoretical Biology 29 (1970): 471-81.